This is an automated broadcast
from the Greenland Maritime Safety Information Service.
The following information
is valid for the next 24 hours.
Weather forecast for waters
off the south west coast of Greenland.
Northeast, force 5 to 6, increasing to force 7 in exposed areas.
Moderate to rough, becoming very rough in open waters.
Poor, with fog patches, improving to moderate by afternoon.
Two to four. One.
Navigation warning: A strict no-sail zone has been established around Ravnedod due to electromagnetical interference and ongoing research.
All vessels are prohibited
from entering the area bounded by the following coordinates.
63°45'N, 051°35'W, 63°45'N, 051°15'W...
*static*